Eugene Van Cleef Papers 1906-1973 Mss.Ms.Coll.61
American Philosophical Society
- Series VI. Publication reviews, 1929-1963; 0.2 lin. feet
  - Story of the Weather, n.d. (Box 10)
  - This Business World, 1937 (Box 10)
  - Trade Centers and Routes, 1937 (Box 10)